Finding Aid for the Herschel Burke Gilbert Papers PASC-M.0268
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Associations & Organizations, Series 6.
  - Film Music Society, 2002 (Box 243)
    Honorary Building Committee, Jack Lemmon and Gregory Peck, co-chairmen, information package
  - Film Music Society (Box 243)
    6381 Hollywood Blvd floor plan
  - Film Music Society (Box 243)
    bank documents
  - Film Music Society, 2001 (Box 243)
    income and expense documents
  - Film Music Society, 2001 (Box 292)
    Letters between H. B. Gilbert and Elmer Bernstein dated March 15, 2001 regarding Film Music society; letter from Elmer Bernstein to Ms. Jeannie Pool dated March 15, 2001 regarding Film Music Center and the capital money drive.
  - Film Music Society, 2000-2001 (Box 292)
    correspondence to and from Gilbert and Elmer Bernstein
  - Film Music Society, 1999 December 13 (Box 292)
    documents including agenda for December 13, 1999 board meeting, profit and loss statement, by-laws, resume for Ronald K. Dollinger
  - Film Music Society, 2001 (Box 293)
    correspondence, financial papers, minutes of meetings
  - Film Music Society, 1995-2003 (Box 293)
    correspondence and financial papers
  - Film Music Society (Box 293)
    copy of signatures of Dustin Hoffman, Glenn Close and Dick Van Dyke accepting to serve as an Ambassador of Goodwill of the Film Music Society
  - Film Music Society (Box 293)
    List of Honorary Co-Chairs Jack Lemmon and Gregory Peck and Ambassadors of Goodwill
  - Film Music Society, 2000 (Box 293)
    Capital campaign 2000, correspondence and proposals for funding including for the Film Music Museum's Hall at the Motion Picture Hall of Fame 2003
  - Film Music Society, 2001 October 4; audio cassette (Box 296)
    meeting at UCLA
  - Film Music Society - The Cue Sheet Newsletter, 1989-2001 (Box 243)
    The Cue Sheet newsletter: v.6, no. 1-3 (Feb-Jul 1989), v.7, no.3 (Jul 1990), v. 8, no. 1,3 (Mar, Sep 1991), v.9, no.3 (Jul 1992), v.17,no.2-3 (Apr-Jul 2001), Journal of the Film Music Society, formerly known as the Society for the Preservation of Film Music
  - Film Music Society - The Cue Sheet Newsletter, 1998-2000 (Box 243)
    The Cue Sheet: the Newsletter of the Society for the Preservation of Film Music V14N1-3(1998)V5N1(1988)V6N1-2(1989), V8N3(1991)V9N1,3(1992)V12N1(1996)V15N3-4(1999)V16N3-4(2000)
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music), 1996 (Box 243)
    Film Music Collections in the U.S., published by The Society for the Preservation of Film Music, 1996 guide to collection
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music) (Box 243)
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music), 2001 (Box 243)
    score, letter, historical documents: 5th Annual Career Achievement Award to Elmer Bernstein. Dec. 19, 1988, score for tribute - lyrics, new music and routine by Jay Livingston and Ray Evans.
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music) (Box 243)
    tax forms
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music), 1993 (Box 266)
    Tribute to Hans J. Salter
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music), 1993; v (Box 266)
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music), 1993; VHS (Box 266)
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music), 1993; VHS (Box 266)
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music), 1991 (Box 266)
    Tribute to John Williams
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music), 1991; VHS (Box 266)
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music), 1991 July (Box 271)
    "The Cue Sheet" v. 8, no. 2 (July 1991) - journal of the Society for the Preservation of Film Music, H.B. Gilbert with the Louis C. Schnauber Silent Film music collection
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music) (Box 292)
    pamphlet containing list of trustees, advisors, history and goals of the society, and description of the National Union Catalogue of Film Music
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music) (Box 292)
    pamphlet and membership application
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music), 1991 (Box 293)
    Proposal for funding to the David and Lucile Packard Foundation, the National Project for Film Music Preservation and Documentation submitted by Jeannie Pool, Exec Director Society for the Preservation of Film Music
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music) (Box 293)
    Proposal for funding
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music ), 1996 (Box 293)
    Film Music Collections in the US: a guide, H Stephen Wright, editor, published by the Society for the Preservation of Film Music
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music), 1992 June 6 (Box 293)
    Board of Trustees Meeting, UCLA Sunset Canyon Recreation Center, binder of documents for the meeting.
  - Film Music Society (Society for the Preservation of Film Music), 1992 (Box 293)
    invitation to the Tribute Gala Event for Career Achievement Award Tribute honoring Henry Mancini
  - Gardner Elementary School, 1969 (Box 263)
    "Ham on Wry": (Original Musical for Gardner Elementary School 1969)
  - Gardner Elementary School Community Advisory Counsil (Box 285)
    sample documents
  - Hollywood High School Community Advisory Council (Box 285)
  - Hollywood Mental Health Service (Box 285)
    Hollywood Citizens Liason Committee sample documents
  - Hollywood Motion Picture Hall of Fame (Box 243)
    Information and sponsorship package.
  - Hollywood Motion Picture Hall of Fame, 2002 (Box 243)
    Press Release
  - Hollywood Motion Picture Hall of Fame (Box 243)
    Executive Summary Report.
  - Hollywood Motion Picture Hall of Fame (Box 293)
    Executive Summary
  - International Confederation of Societies of Authors and Composers, 1975 April 21-26 (Box 246)
    World Congress of Authors and Composers, 29th Congress (Hamburg) proceedings documents
  - Juilliard Alumni Association, 1961-1967 (Box 246)
    documents, correspondence, letters, minutes, some contain photographs
  - Juilliard Alumni Association (Box 285)
    Southern California Chapter sample documents
  - Juilliard Auditions at Los Angeles, 1962 (Box 247)
  - Los Angeles Musician and The Music Performance Trust Funds, 1956 January (Box 286)
    The Los Angeles Musician and The Music Performance Trust Funds, An economic study for Musicians' Mutual Protective Association Local No. 47, American Federation of Musicians.
  - memos, rules booklets, eligible releases (including 1952 - The Moon is Blue), membership lists, 1951-1956 (Box 249)
  - Musician's Union Local 47, 1956 January (Box 286)
    Appeal of Local 47 Before the International Executive Board American Federation of Musicians.
  - National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences, 1993 (Box 271)
    Journal, v. 4, no. 1 (Summer 1993), journal provides a scholarly analysis of business, technology and trends within
  - National Academy of Recording Arts and Sciences, 1993 (Box 271)
    Journal, v. 4, no. 1 (Summer 1993), journal provides a scholarly analysis of business, technology and trends within the music and recording industry.
  - National Film Music Council, 1950-1958 (Box 271)
    Official publication of the National Film Music Council: "Film Music Notes" special issue 1949, v. 9, no. 4 ( March-April 1950); "Film Music" v. 11, no. 4 (March-April 1952);"Film Music" v. 12, no. 1-5(September 1952-June 1953) - no. 2 is about "The Thief"; v.13, no. 2,4,5(November 1953-June 1954), v.14, no. 1-3(September 1954-February 1955)v. 15, no. 3 (Jan-Feb 1956); "Film and TV Music" v. 17, no. 1(Fall and Winter 1957-58)
  - Nichols Canyon Association (Box 285)
  - Publisher Advisory Committee Members, 1966 (Box 261)
  - Rotary Club (Box 285)
  - Rotary Club of Hollywood (Box 271)
    member information
  - SCA, 1975-1979; audio cassette (Box 297)
    board meetings.
  - Screen Composer's Association, 1946-1967 (Box 244)
    bulletins, reports: 1946, 1947, 1956, 1965, 1967
  - Screen Composer's Association (Box 244)
    correspondence, historical background on founding of SCA, letters, membership lists
  - Screen Composer's Association, 1954-1967 (Box 245)
    correspondence 1954-1967
  - Screen Composers' Associations, 1954 (Box 246)
    letters and membership lists
  - Screen Composers' Association, 1966 (Box 246)
    Retainer agreement and blank member application forms
  - Screen Composers' Association, 1972-1973 (Box 246)
    minutes
  - Screen Composers' Association, 1967-1972 (Box 246)
  - Screen Composers' Association, 1966 January (Box 246)
    agreement, constitution and by-laws
  - Screen Composers' Association, 1966 (Box 247)
    bulletin July 1966 edition
  - Screen Composers' Association (Box 247)
    television monitoring report with general instructions for monitors
  - Screen Composers' Association of the United States of America, 1966 April (Box 247)
    Agreement, constitution and by-laws amended
  - Screen Composers' Association, 1960-1966 (Box 247)
    documents, correspondence, minutes
  - Screen Composers' Association, 1958 (Box 248)
    press release, first honorary awards to Max Steiner and Andre Previn
  - Screen Composers' Association, 1958 May 15 (Box 248)
    Award celebration, includes telegrams of congratulations to Andre Previn and Max Steiner
  - Screen Composers' Association, 1958 May 15 (Box 248)
  - Screen Composers' Association, 1947-1956 (Box 248)
    Bulletin, September 1947, December 1947, June 1948, August 1948, April 1949, November 1949, January 1953, November 1953, December 1953, July 1954, January 1956
  - Screen Composers' Association, 1959 (Box 248)
  - Screen Composers' Association, 1960 (Box 248)
  - Screen Composers' Association (Box 248)
    sample stationery
  - Screen Composers' Association, 1957 (Box 248)
    Awards Committee screening rules, includes official nomination ballot for Best Picture of the Year Award for the 30th Annual Academy Awards
  - Screen Composers' Association, 1958 (Box 248)
  - Screen Composers' Association, 1958 (Box 248)
    Awards Committee questionnaire
  - Screen Composers' Association, documents, correspondence, minutes 1958-1965 no.2-3 (Apr-Jul 2001), Journal of the Film Music Society, formerly known as the Society for the Preservation of Film Music (Box 248)
  - Screen Composers of America (SCA) and Composers & Lyricists Guild of America (CLGA) (Box 274)
    Material relating to Screen Composers of America (SCA) and Composers & Lyricists Guild of America (CLGA) including minutes of meetings, applications, retainers, billings, composers' class action law suit, and correspondence, agreements
  - Screen Composers of America (SCA) (Box 275)
    Material relating to Screen Composers of America (SCA) including minutes of meetings, applications, retainers, billings, correspondence, financial reports, legal and billing expenses, achievements, agreements
  - Screen Composers of America (SCA) (Box 276)
    Material relating to Screen Composers of America (SCA) Elmer Bernstein v. Universal lawsuit, Goldsmith trial, membership information, international societies and conferences (e.g. CISAC - Confederation Internationale des Societes D'Auteurs et Compositeurs)
  - Screen Composers of America (SCA), 1945-1976 (Box 277)
    Material relating to Screen Composers of America (SCA) including membership info, Zissu & Marcus correspondence and retainer agreements, membership information 1945-1976, stationery, financial reports
  - Screen Directors' Guild of America, 1950-1954 (Box 247)
    Basic Agreement of 1950 with Independent producers - IMPPA modified in 1951, 52, & 1954
  - Screen Writers' Guild (Box 247)
    credits manual
  - Screen Writers' Guild, 1951 (Box 247)
  - Southern California Chapter of Los Angeles of the Juilliard Alumni Association, Directory, 1960-1961 (Box 246)
  - Tariff Controls Committee (Box 247)
  - The Society of Composers & Lyricists, 1988-1990 (Box 280)
    The Score, booklet of The Society of Composers & Lyricists: Winter 1990, Summer 1990, Spring 1990, Winter 1989, Summer 1989, Spring 1989, Winter 1988
  - Tribute to Helen Forest Ventura Club, audio cassette (Box 296)
  - University of Wyoming (Box 271)
    University of Wyoming correspondence soliciting Herschel Gilbert documents, refers to their receipt of Harry James recordings
  - Wattles Farm and Neighborhood Gardners (Box 285)
  - World Conference of Authors & Composers, 1975 April 21-26 (Box 255)
    CISAC - Hamburg, April 21-26, 1975 World Conference of Authors & Composers - documents, notes, photos
  - Writers Guild of America, 1955 (Box 271)
    Writing credit lists
- Contracts and Agreements, Series 7.
  - "Bailout at 43,000", "The Big Caper", "The Monster that Challenged the World", and "The Vampire" Zissu, Marcus & Stein, 1966 (Box 267)
  - "Christmas is a Time for Children" song agreement with John Paul Music Corp and Carmino Ravosa and record-music report and for the song "Civilization", 1959 (Box 279)
  - "Full of Love" song music by Heinz Roemheld lyric by Alan Bergman and Marilyn Keith Uniform Popular Songwriters Contract for song based on the theme from the United Artists picture "The Monster that Challenged the World", 1957 (Box 279)
  - "Georgia Ann" song words and music by Hylton R. Socher, correspondence and agreement with John Paul Music Corp., 1959 (Box 279)
  - "Ha-Bee-Bee-Rock" music and words by Edward E. Ocnoff, Uniform Popular Songwriters Contract, 1957 (Box 279)
  - "Haven't You Heard" music and words by Joe Mullendore and Uniform Popular Songwriters Contract with John Paul Music Corp., 1958 (Box 279)
  - "How Wrong You Are" song music by Hylton Socher lyrics by Ronald Miller, Uniform Popular Songwriters Contract with John Paul Music Corp and correspondence including promotion with WAMO radio Pittsburgh, PA, 1958 (Box 279)
  - "If You're Asking Me" song music by Albert Glasser lyrics by Alan Bergman and Marilyn Keith, Uniform Popular Songwriters Contract (Box 279)
  - "If You're Asking Me" song music by Albert Glasser lyrics by Alan Bergman and Marilyn Keith, Uniform Popular Songwriters Contractwith John Paul Music Corp., 1957 (Box 279)
  - "Lost Love" song music by Ernst Jacobi & Bill Marky words by Loren Gardner, agreement with John Paul Music Corp., 1959 (Box 279)
  - "Now I Believe" song, music and words by Carl Ravosa, agreement with John Paul Music Corp., 1959 (Box 279)
  - "Oh Daddy" music and words by Gary Jonke and Mike Metzger, agreement and Certificate of Registration of claim to Copyright, 1958 (Box 279)
  - "One Night in Acapulco" song words and music by Buddy Baker and Joe Mullendore, Uniform Popular Songwriters Contract, 1958 (Box 279)
  - "Simple Folk" song, music and words by Carmino Ravosa, agreement with John Paul Music Corp., 1958 (Box 279)
  - "Stolen Fruit" song, music and words by Carmino Ravosa, agreement with John Paul Music Corp., 1958 (Box 279)
  - "Talking Over You" song, music and words by Carmino Ravosa, agreement with John Paul Music corp and Certificate of Registration of a claim to Copyright, 1958 (Box 279)
  - "The Thought of Christmas" song, music by Carmino Ravosa lyric by Jon Shepodd, agreement with John Paul Music Corp., 1959 (Box 279)
  - "This Town Isn't Big Enough for Both of Us" song, words and music by Joe Mullendore, Uniform Popular Songwriters Contract 1958 and correspondence (Box 279)
  - "Tight, White Capris" song, music by Edward Ocnoff lyric by Lee Bishop & Edward Ocnoff, Uniform Popular Songwriters Contract, 1959 (Box 279)
  - "Twenty Mule Train" song, music by Herb Taylor lyrics by Milton Raskin, agreement between John Paul Music Corp and Decca Records, 1959 (Box 279)
    includes royalty statements
  - "Who Knows" song, music by Albert Glasser lyrics by A. Bergman and M. Keith (Box 279)
    Uniform Popular Songwriters Contract 1957, correspondence and newspaper clipping from "The Cash Box, Music" August 3, 1957, pg. 14 "Best Bets"
  - "Wicked Woman" and "One Night in Acapulco", 1958, 1966 (Box 267)
  - "Wicked Woman" song, music by Norman Dale and Joe Mullendore, Uniform Popular Songwriters Contract 1958, includes correspondence and cue sheets (Box 279)
  - 20th Century record corporation and John Paul Music Corp regarding the purchase of master contracts for the Art Tatum tapes 1959 (Box 279)
    Includes correspondence and agreements
  - Agreement between Herschel Burke Gilbert and Martin J. Machat and Lamas Music, a Division of RKO, 1957 February 28 (Box 251)
  - Agreement between John Paul Music & Nazionalmusic Organizzazione Musicale re: royalties representation in Italy, 1965 (Box 252)
  - Agreement between Mirisch Bros. Productions, Inc. & United Artists Corporation, 1957 July 19 (Box 289)
  - Agreement between Mirisch Bros. International Productions, Inc. & United Artists Corporation, 1957 July 19 (Box 289)
  - American Federation of Musicians, 1970 April 1 (Box 248)
    Personal Service Contract for The French Way, multiple employees
  - American Federation of Musicians Phonograph Record Labor Agreement for HB Gilbert and DBAs, 1984 August (Box 251)
  - ASCAP (Box 249)
    Blank Application for Publisher-Membership in ASCAP, 1950s
  - Ashley Famous Agency Inc agreement with Herschel Burke Gilbert, 1966 August 31 (Box 251)
  - Assignments - Cues 1-90 from Dave Chudnow for Byron Music Company, Mutel (Box 284)
  - Bailout at 43,000, The Monster That Challenged the World, The Big Caper, The Vampire (Box 289)
  - Basic agreement for independent motion picture producers (Box 247)
  - BMI Publisher agreement with Gilbey Music Company, 1963 (Box 267)
  - CBS Radio (Box 247)
    blank contract for employment as a composer for the preparation of musical themes, bridges, and cues
  - Chartwell Artists - "Summer of '42", 1969-1970 (Box 268)
  - Consortium Records, articles of incorporation of Consortium recordings (Box 271)
  - Correspondence and agreements with Bourne, Inc (Saul Bourne and then Bonnie Bourne) (Box 254)
  - Correspondence re: accounting (John McCutcheon), rights, Chappell, Martin Machat, 1957-1967 (Box 253)
  - Definition of Net Profits, Agreement for songs, 1965 (Box 252)
  - Executed agreements (Box 284)
    : Whiskey's Renegades, Carmen Jones, No Place to Hide, News is Made at Night, The Four Seasons, The Bold and the Brave, Nightmare, Comanche, A Man is as Good as His Word, Beyond a Reasonable Doubt, Crime and Punishment (not signed), Slaughter on Tenth Avenue cover letter only, 1976 communications re: rights
  - Gilbey Music Company, 1977-1978 (Box 267)
  - Gilbey Music Company for various television films, 1963 (Box 267)
  - IMUA agreement with Frank Tavares, 1971 (Box 272)
    (known professionally as Palani Kawalea), sheet music and list of music and songs authored and/or composed by Frank Tavares assigned to IMUA Music Company
  - IMUA Music Company blank agreement, "Variety" newspaper clipping 1971, correspondence and blank sample of IMUA letterhead (Box 272)
  - John Paul (Box 241)
    standard forms
  - John Paul (Box 241)
    John Paul, Songwriters' Protective Association: Blank forms
  - John Paul (Box 241)
    Ocnoff
  - John Paul (Box 241)
    Bergman/Keith/Roemheld, 4 titles
  - John Paul (Box 241)
    Durand
  - John Paul (Box 241)
    Ravosa/Shepodd
  - John Paul, 1957-1961 (Box 242)
    Mutel with John Paul Music and Herschel Burke Gilbert
  - John Paul (Box 242)
    Herschel Burke Gilbert and John Paul Music with Synchro Sound including correspondence
  - John Paul, 1976 December 1 (Box 249)
    Agreement Between Herschel Burke Gilbert doing business as John Paul Music and ASCAP
  - John Paul, 1957 March 21 (Box 249)
    ASCAP certificate of election to membership, John Paul Music Corp on March 21, 1957
  - John Paul Music, 1994 (Box 251)
    Agreement with Tee Vee Toons, Inc and John Paul Music, unsigned
  - John Paul Music, 1958-1963 (Box 252)
    Licenses granted
  - John Paul Music (Box 253)
    Agreement and correspondence between John Paul Music and Edward Ocnoff
  - John Paul Music (Box 253)
    Various music licenses
  - John Paul Music, 1957-1965 (Box 253)
    Contract - RKO Television, Lamas Music with John Paul Music plus correspondence
  - John Paul Music (Box 253)
    Recording license forms for John Paul Music and Gilbey Music
  - John Paul Music, 1958 (Box 253)
    1947 Revised Uniform Popular Songwriters Contract, 1958, John Paul Music with Ronald S. Miller & Hylton R. Socher
  - John Paul Music, 1956 (Box 261)
    John Paul Music Certificate of Incorporation
  - John Paul Music, 1958 (Box 267)
    John Paul Music Corporation with Leonard J. Warren
  - John Paul Music, 1962 (Box 268)
    John Paul Music Corp. for various compositions by H.G. Gilbert and Ernie Hughes
  - License forms for use of music (and correspondence on Four Star letterhead) (Box 252)
  - Major motion picture contract, summary of revisions May 1955, 1955 May (Box 247)
  - Marlen Music Company, motion picture agreements, 1950-1953 (Box 269)
  - Minimum prices for music composition per picture and/or per minute basis, 1955 July (Box 247)
  - Motion Picture minimum wage chart - includes budget of picture, rate per minute, minutes of music up to and including 60 (Box 247)
  - Mutel Corporation original contracts, original filing sheets & recoding code & list of cues (Box 284)
  - Mutel with John Paul Music and Herschel Burke Gilbert, 1957-1961 (Box 242)
  - Producer - Screen Actors Guild, Codified Basic Agreement of 1952 (Box 247)
  - Radio Writers' Guild, 1947 (Box 247)
    Network Freelance Minimum Basis Agreement, and The Producers and Radio Writers Guild
  - Revised Uniform Popular Songwriters Contract, 1947 (Box 241)
  - Revised Uniform Popular Songwriters Contract Sept 15, 1957 between John Paul Music Corp & Edward Ocnoff, 1947 (Box 252)
  - RKO (1955) and Allied Artists Productions (1953), 1953, 1955 (Box 268)
  - Sandre Films of Colorado, 1949-1956 (Box 269)
  - Screen Actors Guild, 1952 (Box 247)
    Producer Television contract
  - Screen Actors Guild, 1955 (Box 247)
    Producer codified contract for filmed commercials
  - Screen Directors' Guild, 1952 (Box 247)
    television contracts
  - Screen Writers' Guild, 1955 (Box 247)
    motion picture contract
  - Screen Writers' Guild, 1953-1955 (Box 247)
  - Screen Writers' Guild, 1951 (Box 247)
    independent producers agreement
  - Screenplay contract "The Whistling Shadow", Mr. John Briard Harding, 1955-1956 (Box 269)
  - Settlement agreement with RKO-Lamas and related correspondence (Box 253)
  - Songs, Bill Mundy, Janice and Bill Mundy (Box 253)
  - Telemount Mutual (Box 284)
    notation "Old" on HB Gilbert's file
  - Telemount Mutual - notation "Old" on HB Gilbert's file (Box 284)
  - Undated agreement between Unique Record Manufacturing Corp and Max Steiner, 1957 (Box 251)
  - William Morris Agency, composing contracts and related information, 1952-1953 (Box 269)
  - Woman With a Whip, music composed by Harry Sukman (Box 289)
- Rights and Royalties, Series 8.
  - Accounting from Chappell & Co. Ltd., 1966 (Box 250)
  - ASCAP, 1958-1970 (Box 250)
    Correspondence between Herschel Burke Gilbert and ASCAP regarding foreign royalties
  - ASCAP letter to John Paul Music re: termination of Chappell & Co (Box 251)
  - ASCAP Proposed Consent Order, 1959 (Box 260)
  - ASCAP Proposed Consent Order, 1960 (Box 261)
    Weighting formula.
  - ASCAP Proposed Consent Order, 1959 (Box 261)
  - ASCAP re: John Paul Music/Edizione Musicali (Kassner), 1964 (Box 261)
    Italy dispute.
  - ASCAP re: John Paul Music Cues, 1964 (Box 261)
    ASCAP re: John Paul Music cues: Robert Taylor Detective Series: Crime & Punishment
  - ASCAP royalty payment stubs, John Paul Music 1960s (Box 251)
  - ASCAP royalty payment stubs, HB Gilbert, 1960s (Box 251)
  - Ballad of the Big Bankroll (Box 289)